You follow me on Tik Tok?
>> Yep.
>> Really?
>> Yes.
>> Well, man, hey, life been crazy right
now, but I'm still out here doing
things, man, and uh
>> I follow I follow you on that, and I
watched you where the city was giving
you hell about the houses and all.
>> Yeah.
All of them.
Hey, yeah, they still doing that, but we
still out here swinging, man, you know?
The system is tough on people. Would you
agree?
>> Oh, yeah. It it Our county where I'm
from,
they they they really
they they make it hard on everybody.
>> I think
>> And they constantly raise our taxes, but
they don't want to do what's benefit us
in any shape, way, or form.
>> Well, I think life is hard for everybody
right now, and we'll just keep pushing
forward.
>> That's all we can do.
>> That's it, my guy.
Yeah.
I'm in Augusta right now, working
through things, and life is very tough,
but everywhere I go, I see friends who
recognize me, and they want to talk. Um
I know life is hard for everyone, but
remember, you just got to keep pushing
forward. Every day is not great, but
it's a little bit better than the day
before, and uh progress, not perfection,
is the motto right now. Uh I know
content hasn't been what it's been
lately, but I'm still out here swinging.
I have some amazing things in the works,
just not talking about them much, cuz
I'm working so hard. And uh you will see
some more from Joe. Sending y'all love
from Augusta, Georgia.